shoptrailblazer.com 2014-12-16

# Denali Privacy Policy

**Customer Service**

#### Shipping Policy  
Return Policy  
Locations  
FAQs  
About Us  
Contact Us  
Privacy Policy  
Affiliate Program  
Price Match Policy  
Gift Card Balance

| 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
When placing an order we collect your name, address, email address, telephone and credit card information. This information is stored confidentially and is only used to process your order and notify you of the order status. We collect the e-mail addresses of visitors to our site and aggregate (not personally identifiable) information on what pages visitors access. We use this information to monitor the use of the site and to improve its performance and usefulness. We also collect information you volunteer, such as survey responses, comments, purchasing and billing information, and your requests. Finally we collect email address for those who wish to receive coupons, promotions, and updates from [DenaliOutdoor.com](http://www.denalioutdoor.com/) or our Denali Store location. This information we collect will not be sold or shared with any other company and is used for Denali Outdoor only!

**How do we protect customer information?**  
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

We will not sell, share, trade, or give away any personal information that we receive regarding our customers.We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**How do we allow customers to update or change the information we collect?**  
You may update or change information related to your account by updating your profile, accessible via the home page once you are logged in, or by sending us email.Yes, we do use cookies, but we do not overuse them! We use cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience. The text in a cookie, by itself, only tells us that you have visited our site before. It does not store any personal information such as your name, e-mail address, street address, or phone number. Cookies are also used to maintain your shopping basket. All data contained in the shopping basked is kept on our server and not in the cookie your machine is assigned.

**Your consent**  
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Tell us what you think**  
We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. If you have any questions, please [email ](mailto:service@denalioutdoor.com)us.
